<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Commissions on The Amazing World of Gumball</title>
    <link>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Commissions on The Amazing World of Gumball</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <atom:link href="https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Flat Color</title>
      <link>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/flat-color/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/flat-color/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;A flat color is an area of color painted in a uniform or identical tone and hue, but getting acrylic paints to dry completely flat and streak-free can be challenging for beginner painters.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Fortunately, there are a number of techniques to help painters flatten their images, providing crisp backgrounds and splashes of color in paintings.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Simple Shaded</title>
      <link>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/simple-shaded/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/simple-shaded/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shading is the technique used in drawing to create the illusion of depth and volume on a two-dimensional surface by manipulating light and shadow.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This process helps define the form of objects, providing a sense of realism and dimensionality. By understanding how light interacts with various shapes, artists can depict basic forms like cubes, spheres, cylinders, and cones more effectively, as well as complex subjects such as facial features.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Full Shaded</title>
      <link>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/full-shaded/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/full-shaded/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Shading adds depth and volume to drawings by creating contrasts between light and dark areas, which help define the shape of objects.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;When an artist applies shading correctly, it enhances the viewer&amp;rsquo;s perception of three-dimensionality. This technique allows even simple forms like cubes and spheres to appear more realistic by mimicking how light interacts with these objects.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Monochrome</title>
      <link>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/monochrome/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/monochrome/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Grayscale images, are black-and-white or gray monochrome, and composed exclusively of shades of gray. The contrast ranges from black at the weakest intensity to white at the strongest.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Grayscale images are distinct from one-bit bi-tonal black-and-white images, which, in the context of computer imaging, are images with only two colors: black and white (also called bilevel or binary images). Grayscale images have many shades of gray in between.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Icon</title>
      <link>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/icon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://kryst4line.github.io/hugo-pictochat/commissions/icon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The purpose of a profile picture is to provide others with a visual identity or representation of the individual in the online realm. It helps to personalize the user’s online presence and can contribute to establishing their online persona or brand. The profile picture is often the primary visual element that others see when interacting with the user’s profile or content.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
